<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
 <codehawk-binary-analyzer>
  <reference href="http://msdn.microsoft.com/"/>
  <header date="03/08/2015 19:08:44"/>
  <libfun lib="advapi32" name="CryptGetProvParam">
   <documentation>
    <desc>
      retrieves parameters that govern the operations of a cryptographic 
      service provider (CSP).
    </desc>
    <apidoc>
     <pt>
      <ll>BOOL WINAPI CryptGetProvParam(</ll>
      <ld>_In_     HCRYPTPROV hProv</ld>
      <ld>_In_     DWORD dwParam</ld>
      <ld>_Out_    BYTE *pbData</ld>
      <ld>_Inout_  DWORD *pdwDataLen</ld>
      <ld>_In_     DWORD dwFlags</ld>
      <ll>)</ll>
     </pt>
     <par name="hProv">
       A handle of the CSP target of the query. This handle must have been 
       created by using the CryptAcquireContext function.
     </par>
     <par name="dwParam">The nature of the query</par>
     <par name="pbData">
       A pointer to a buffer to receive the data. The form of this data varies 
       depending on the value of dwParam. When dwParam is set to 
       PP_USE_HARDWARE_RNG, pbData must be set to NULL.
       This parameter can be NULL to set the size of this information for 
       memory allocation purposes
     </par>
     <par name="pdwDataLen">
       A pointer to a DWORD value that specifies the size, in bytes, of the buffer 
       pointed to by the pbData parameter. When the function returns, the DWORD 
       value contains the number of bytes stored or to be stored in the buffer.
       Note  When processing the data returned in the buffer, applications must 
       use the actual size of the data returned. The actual size can be slightly 
       smaller than the size of the buffer specified on input. (On input, buffer 
       sizes are usually specified large enough to ensure that the largest possible 
       output data fits in the buffer.) On output, the variable pointed to by this 
       parameter is updated to reflect the actual size of the data copied to the 
       buffer.
       If PP_ENUMALGS, or PP_ENUMALGS_EX is set, the pdwDataLen parameter works 
       somewhat differently. If pbData is NULL or the value pointed to by pdwDataLen 
       is too small, the value returned in this parameter is the size of the 
       largest item in the enumeration list instead of the size of the item
       currently being read.
       If PP_ENUMCONTAINERS is set, the first call to the function returns the 
       size of the maximum key-container allowed by the current provider. This 
       is in contrast to other possible behaviors, like returning the length of 
       the longest existing container, or the length of the current container. 
       Subsequent enumerating calls will not change the dwLen parameter. For
       each enumerated container, the caller can determine the length of the 
       null-terminated string programmatically, if desired. If one of the
       enumeration values is read and the pbData parameter is NULL, the CRYPT_FIRST 
       flag must be specified for the size information to be correctly retrieved.
     </par>
     <par name="dwFlags">
       If dwParam is PP_KEYSET_SEC_DESCR, the security descriptor on the key 
       container where the keys are stored is retrieved. For this case, dwFlags 
       is used to pass in the SECURITY_INFORMATION bit flags that indicate the 
       requested security information, as defined in the Platform SDK. 
       SECURITY_INFORMATION bit flags can be combined with a bitwise-OR operation.
     </par>
     <return>
      <rc cond="success">nonzero</rc>
      <rc cond="failure">zero</rc>
     </return>
    </apidoc>
   </documentation>
   <api adj="20" cc="stdcall" name="CryptGetProvParam">
    <par loc="stack" io="r" name="hProv" nr="1">
     <type>HCRYPTPROV</type>
     <pre><deref-read/></pre>
     <roles>
       <role rt="ioc:crypto" rn="handle:CSP"/>
     </roles>
    </par>
    <par loc="stack" io="r" name="dwParam" roles="none" nr="2">
     <type>DWORD</type>
     <pre><enum-value name="crypt_get_prov_param_query_type"/></pre>
     <rep type="enum" name="crypt_get_prov_param_query_type"/>
    </par>
    <par loc="stack" io="w" name="pbData" rep="hex" nr="3">
     <type><ptr>BYTE</ptr></type>
     <roles>
       <role rt="ioc:crypto" rn="infox:key blob data"/>
     </roles>
    </par>
    <par loc="stack" io="rw" name="pdwDataLen" nr="4">
     <type><ptr>DWORD</ptr></type>
     <pre><deref-read/></pre>
     <sideeffects><block-write/></sideeffects>
     <roles>
       <role rt="size:actual" rn="CryptGetProvParam"/>
     </roles>
    </par>
    <par loc="stack" name="dwFlags" roles="none" nr="5">
      <type>DWORD</type>
    </par>
    <returntype>BOOL</returntype>
   </api>
   <semantics>
     <io-actions>
       <io-action cat="crypto"
		  desc="retrieves parameters that govern the operations of a cryptographic service provider (CSP)"/>
     </io-actions>
    <preconditions>
      <pre>
	<math>
	  <apply>
	    <deref-write-null/>
	    <type>byte</type>
	    <ci>pbData</ci>
	    <apply><addressed-value/><ci>pdwDataLen</ci><cn>0</cn></apply>
	  </apply>
	</math>
      </pre>
    </preconditions>
    <postconditions>
     <nonzero-zero/>
    </postconditions>
    <sideeffects>
      <sideeffect>
	<math>
	  <apply>
	    <block-write/>
	    <type>byte</type>
	    <ci>pbData</ci>
	    <apply><addressed-value/><ci>pdwDataLen</ci><cn>0</cn></apply>
	  </apply>
	</math>
      </sideeffect>
    </sideeffects>
   </semantics>
  </libfun>
  <copyright-notice>Copyright 2012-2016, Kestrel Technology LLC, Palo Alto, CA 94304</copyright-notice>
 </codehawk-binary-analyzer>
