<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
 <codehawk-binary-analyzer>
  <reference href="http://msdn.microsoft.com/"/>
  <header date="08/18/2015 16:03:46"/>
  <libfun lib="user32" name="mouse_event">
   <documentation>
    <desc>synthesizes mouse motion and button clicks</desc>
    <apidoc>
     <pt>
      <ll>VOID WINAPI mouse_event(</ll>
      <ld>_In_ DWORD     dwFlags</ld>
      <ld>_In_ DWORD     dx</ld>
      <ld>_In_ DWORD     dy</ld>
      <ld>_In_ DWORD     dwData</ld>
      <ld>_In_ ULONG_PTR dwExtraInfo</ld>
      <ll>)</ll>
     </pt>
     <par name="dwFlags">Controls various aspects of mouse motion and button clicking</par>
     <par name="dx">
       The mouse's absolute position along the x-axis or its amount of motion since 
       the last mouse event was generated, depending on the setting of 
       MOUSEEVENTF_ABSOLUTE. Absolute data is specified as the mouse's actual x-coordinate; 
       relative data is specified as the number of mickeys moved. A mickey is the amount 
       that a mouse has to move for it to report that it has moved.
     </par>
     <par name="dy">
       The mouse's absolute position along the y-axis or its amount of motion since the
       last mouse event was generated, depending on the setting of MOUSEEVENTF_ABSOLUTE. 
       Absolute data is specified as the mouse's actual y-coordinate; relative data is 
       specified as the number of mickeys moved.
     </par>
     <par name="dwData">
       If dwFlags contains MOUSEEVENTF_WHEEL, then dwData specifies the amount of wheel 
       movement. A positive value indicates that the wheel was rotated forward, away 
       from the user; a negative value indicates that the wheel was rotated backward,
       toward the user. One wheel click is defined as WHEEL_DELTA, which is 120.
       If dwFlags contains MOUSEEVENTF_HWHEEL, then dwData specifies the amount of wheel 
       movement. A positive value indicates that the wheel was tilted to the right; a 
       negative value indicates that the wheel was tilted to the left.
       If dwFlags contains MOUSEEVENTF_XDOWN or MOUSEEVENTF_XUP, then dwData specifies
       which X buttons were pressed or released. This value may be any combination of 
       the following flags.
       If dwFlags is not MOUSEEVENTF_WHEEL, MOUSEEVENTF_XDOWN, or MOUSEEVENTF_XUP, 
       then dwData should be zero.
     </par>
     <par name="dwExtraInfo">
       An additional value associated with the mouse event. An application calls 
       GetMessageExtraInfo to obtain this extra information.
     </par>
     <return/>
    </apidoc>
   </documentation>
   <api adj="20" cc="stdcall" name="mouse_event">
    <par loc="stack" io="r" name="dwFlags" nr="1">
     <type>DWORD</type>
     <roles/>
    </par>
    <par loc="stack" io="r" name="dx" roles="none" nr="2">
     <type>DWORD</type>
    </par>
    <par loc="stack" io="r" name="dy" roles="none" nr="3">
     <type>DWORD</type>
    </par>
    <par loc="stack" io="r" name="dwData" roles="none" nr="4">
     <type>DWORD</type>
    </par>
    <par loc="stack" io="r" name="dwExtraInfo" roles="none" nr="5">
     <type>ULONG_PTR</type>
    </par>
    <returntype>VOID</returntype>
   </api>
   <semantics>
    <io-actions>
       <io-action cat="process" desc="synthesizes mouse motion and button clicks"/>
    </io-actions>
    <preconditions/>
    <postconditions/>
    <sideeffects/>
   </semantics>
  </libfun>
  <copyright-notice>Copyright 2012-2016, Kestrel Technology LLC, Palo Alto, CA 94304</copyright-notice>
 </codehawk-binary-analyzer>
