<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
 <codehawk-binary-analyzer>
  <reference href="http://msdn.microsoft.com/"/>
  <header date="09/27/2015 22:37:11"/>
  <libfun lib="kernel32" name="WaitForSingleObjectEx">
   <documentation>
    <desc>
      Waits until the specified object is in the signaled state,
      an I/O completion routine or asynchronous procedure call (APC) 
      is queued to the thread, or the time-out interval elapses
    </desc>
    <apidoc>
     <pt>
      <ll>DWORD WINAPI WaitForSingleObjectEx(</ll>
      <ld>_In_ HANDLE hHandle</ld>
      <ld>_In_ DWORD  dwMilliseconds</ld>
      <ld>_In_ BOOL   bAlertable</ld>
      <ll>)</ll>
     </pt>
     <par name="hHandle">A handle to the object.</par>
     <par name="dwMilliseconds">
       The time-out interval, in milliseconds. If a nonzero value is 
       specified, the function waits until the object is signaled, an
       I/O completion routine or APC is queued, or the interval elapses.
       If dwMilliseconds is zero, the function does not enter a wait 
       state if the criteria is not met; it always returns immediately.
       If dwMilliseconds is INFINITE, the function will return only when 
       the object is signaled or an I/O completion routine or APC is queued
     </par>
     <par name="bAlertable">
       If this parameter is TRUE and the thread is in the waiting state,
       the function returns when the system queues an I/O completion routine
       or APC, and the thread runs the routine or function. Otherwise, the
       function does not return, and the completion routine or APC function
       is not executed.
       A completion routine is queued when the ReadFileEx or WriteFileEx 
       function in which it was specified has completed. The wait function
       returns and the completion routine is called only if bAlertable is 
       TRUE, and the calling thread is the thread that initiated the read 
       or write operation. An APC is queued when you call QueueUserAPC.
     </par>
     <return>
      <rc cond="success">the event that caused the function to return</rc>
      <rc cond="failure">-1</rc>
     </return>
    </apidoc>
   </documentation>
   <api adj="12" cc="stdcall" name="WaitForSingleObjectEx">
    <par loc="stack" io="r" name="hHandle" nr="1">
     <type>HANDLE</type>
     <roles>
      <role rt="ioc:synchronization" rn="handle:synchronization object" />
     </roles>
     <pre><deref-read/></pre>
    </par>
    <par loc="stack" io="r" name="dwMilliseconds" nr="2">
     <type>DWORD</type>
     <roles>
      <role rt="ioc:synchronization" rn="timeout" />
     </roles>
    </par>
    <par loc="stack" io="r" name="bAlertable" roles="none" nr="3">
     <type>BOOL</type>
    </par>
    <returntype>DWORD</returntype>
   </api>
   <semantics>
     <io-actions>
       <io-action cat="synchronization"
		  desc="waits for an object to be in the signaled state"/>
     </io-actions>
    <preconditions/>
    <postconditions/>
    <sideeffects/>
   </semantics>
  </libfun>
  <copyright-notice>Copyright 2012-2016, Kestrel Technology LLC, Palo Alto, CA 94304</copyright-notice>
 </codehawk-binary-analyzer>
