<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
 <codehawk-binary-analyzer>
  <reference href="http://msdn.microsoft.com/"/>
  <header date="09/10/2015 00:43:49"/>
  <libfun lib="netapi32" name="Netbios">
   <documentation>
    <desc>
      interprets and executes the specified network control block (NCB)
      The Netbios function is provided primarily for applications that were 
      written for the NetBIOS interface and need to be ported to Windows. 
      Applications not requiring compatibility with NetBIOS should use other 
      interfaces, such as Windows Sockets, mailslots, named pipes, RPC, or 
      distributed COM to accomplish tasks similar to those supported by 
      NetBIOS. These other interfaces are more flexible and portable.
    </desc>
    <apidoc>
     <pt>UCHAR Netbios (PNCB pcnb)</pt>
     <par name="pcnb">
       A pointer to an NCB structure that describes the network control block
     </par>
     <return>
       For synchronous requests, the return value is the return code in the NCB structure.
       That value is also returned in the ncb_retcode member of the NCB structure.
       For asynchronous requests, there are the following possibilities:
       If the asynchronous command has already completed when Netbios returns to its 
       caller, the return value is the return code of the NCB structure, just as if 
       it were a synchronous NCB structure.
       If the asynchronous command is still pending when Netbios returns to its caller, 
       the return value is zero.
       If the address specified by the pncb parameter is invalid, the return value is
       NRC_BADNCB.
       If the buffer length specified in the ncb_length member of the NCB structure is 
       incorrect, or if the buffer specified by the ncb_retcode member is protected 
       from write operations, the return value is NRC_BUFLEN.
     </return>
    </apidoc>
   </documentation>
   <api adj="4" cc="stdcall" name="Netbios">
    <par loc="stack" io="r" name="pcnb" nr="1">
     <type><ptr>NCB</ptr></type>
     <roles>
       <role rt="ioc:network" rn="network control block"/>
     </roles>
    </par>
    <returntype>UCHAR</returntype>
   </api>
   <semantics>
     <io-actions>
       <io-action cat="network" desc="interprets and executes the network control block"/>
     </io-actions>
    <preconditions/>
    <postconditions/>
    <sideeffects/>
   </semantics>
  </libfun>
  <copyright-notice>Copyright 2012-2015, Kestrel Technology LLC, Palo Alto, CA 94304</copyright-notice>
 </codehawk-binary-analyzer>
