<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<codehawk-binary-analyzer>
  <header info="libfun" name="CoInitializeSecurity.xml" time="2016-07-12 10:52:54.261918"/>
  <reference href="http://msdn.microsoft.com"/>
  <libfun lib="ole32" name="CoInitializeSecurity">
    <documentation>
      <desc>
	Registers security and sets the default security values for the process
      </desc>
      <apidoc>
        <pt>
          <ll>HRESUL CoInitializeSecurity(</ll>
          <ld>_In_opt_ PSECURITY_DESCRIPTOR        pSecDesc</ld>
          <ld>_In_     LONG                        cAuthSvc</ld>
          <ld>_In_opt_ SOLE_AUTHENTICATION_SERVICE *asAuthSvc</ld>
          <ld>_In_opt_ void                        *pReserved1</ld>
          <ld>_In_     DWORD                       dwAuthnLevel</ld>
          <ld>_In_     DWORD                       dwImpLevel</ld>
          <ld>_In_opt_ void                        *pAuthList</ld>
          <ld>_In_     DWORD                       dwCapabilities</ld>
          <ld>_In_opt_ void                        *pReserved3</ld>
          <ll>)</ll>
        </pt>
        <par name="pSecDesc">
	  The access permissions that a server will use to receive
	  calls. This parameter is used by COM only when a server
	  calls CoInitializeSecurity. Its value is a pointer to one of
	  three types: an AppID, an IAccessControl object, or a
	  SECURITY_DESCRIPTOR, in absolute format. See the Remarks
	  section for more information.
	</par>
        <par name="cAuthSvc">
	  The count of entries in the asAuthSvc parameter. This
	  parameter is used by COM only when a server calls
	  CoInitializeSecurity. If this parameter is 0, no
	  authentication services will be registered and the server
	  cannot receive secure calls. A value of -1 tells COM to
	  choose which authentication services to register, and if
	  this is the case, the asAuthSvc parameter must be
	  NULL. However, Schannel will never be chosen as an
	  authentication service by the server if this parameter is
	  -1.
	</par>
        <par name="asAuthSvc">
	  An array of authentication services that a server is willing
	  to use to receive a call. This parameter is used by COM only
	  when a server calls CoInitializeSecurity. For more
	  information, see SOLE_AUTHENTICATION_SERVICE.
	</par>
        <par name="pReserved1">This parameter is reserved and must be NULL.</par>
        <par name="dwAuthnLevel">
	  The default authentication level for the process. Both
	  servers and clients use this parameter when they call
	  CoInitializeSecurity. COM will fail calls that arrive with a
	  lower authentication level. By default, all proxies will use
	  at least this authentication level. This value should
	  contain one of the authentication level constants. By
	  default, all calls to IUnknown are made at this level.
	</par>
        <par name="dwImpLevel">
	  The default impersonation level for proxies. The value of
	  this parameter is used only when the process is a client. It
	  should be a value from the impersonation level constants,
	  except for RPC_C_IMP_LEVEL_DEFAULT, which is not for use
	  with CoInitializeSecurity.  Outgoing calls from the client
	  always use the impersonation level as specified. (It is not
	  negotiated.) Incoming calls to the client can be at any
	  impersonation level. By default, all IUnknown calls are made
	  with this impersonation level, so even security-aware
	  applications should set this level carefully. To determine
	  which impersonation levels each authentication service
	  supports, see the description of the authentication services
	  in COM and Security Packages. For more information about
	  impersonation levels, see Impersonation.
	</par>
        <par name="pAuthList">
	  A pointer to SOLE_AUTHENTICATION_LIST, which is an array of
	  SOLE_AUTHENTICATION_INFO structures. This list indicates the
	  information for each authentication service that a client
	  can use to call a server. This parameter is used by COM only
	  when a client calls CoInitializeSecurity.
	</par>
        <par name="dwCapabilities">
	  Additional capabilities of the client or server, specified
	  by setting one or more SOLE_AUTHENTICATION_CAPABILITIES
	  values. Some of these value cannot be used simultaneously,
	  and some cannot be set when particular authentication
	  services are being used. For more information about these
	  flags, see the Remarks section.
	</par>
        <par name="pReserved3">This parameter is reserved and must be NULL</par>
        <return>
          <rc cond="success">S_OK</rc>
          <rc cond="failure">error code</rc>
        </return>
      </apidoc>
    </documentation>
    <api adj="36" cc="stdcall" name="CoInitializeSecurity">
      <par loc="stack" name="pSecDesc" io="r" nr="1" rep="hex">
        <type><ptr>SECURITY_DESCRIPTOR</ptr></type>
	<pre><deref-read-null/></pre>
	<roles>
	  <role rt="ioc:memops" rn="src-struct:SECURITY_DESCRIPTOR"/>
	</roles>
      </par>
      <par loc="stack" name="cAuthSvc" io="r" nr="2">
        <type>LONG</type>
	<roles>
	  <role rt="size:buffersize" rn="CoInitializeSecurity"/>
	</roles>
      </par>
      <par loc="stack" name="asAuthSvc" io="r" rep="hex" nr="3">
        <type><ptr>SOLE_AUTHENTICATION_SERVICE</ptr></type>
        <roles>
           <role rt="ioc:memops" rn="src-struct:SOLE_AUTHENTICATION_SERVICES"/>
        </roles>
      </par>
      <par loc="stack" name="pReserved1" io="r" roles="none" nr="4">
        <type><ptr>void</ptr></type>
      </par>
      <par loc="stack" name="dwAuthnLevel" io="r" roles="none" nr="5">
        <type>DWORD</type>
      </par>
      <par loc="stack" name="dwImpLevel" io="r" nr="6">
        <type>DWORD</type>
	<roles>
	  <role rt="ioc:system" rn="impersonation level"/>
	</roles>
      </par>
      <par loc="stack" name="pAuthList" io="r" rep="hex" nr="7">
        <type><ptr>void</ptr></type>
        <roles>
           <role rt="ioc:memops" rn="src-struct:SOLE_AUTHENTICATION_LIST"/>
        </roles>
      </par>
      <par loc="stack" name="dwCapabilities" io="r" rep="hex" nr="8">
        <type>DWORD</type>
	<roles>
	  <role rt="ioc:memops" rn="SOLE_AUTHENTICATION_CAPABILITIES"/>
	</roles>
      </par>
      <par loc="stack" name="pReserved3" io="r" roles="none" nr="9">
        <type><ptr>void</ptr></type>
      </par>
      <returntype>HRESULT</returntype>
    </api>
    <semantics>
      <io-actions>
        <io-action cat="com"
		   desc="registers security and sets the default security values"/>
      </io-actions>
      <preconditions/>
      <postconditions/>
      <sideeffects/>
    </semantics>
  </libfun>
  <copyright-notice>Copyright 2012-2017, Kestrel Technology LLC, Palo Alto, CA 94304</copyright-notice>
</codehawk-binary-analyzer>
