<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<codehawk-binary-analyzer>
  <header info="libfun" name="ProgIDFromCLSID.xml" time="2016-07-02 21:48:02.394305"/>
  <reference href="http://msdn.microsoft.com"/>
  <libfun lib="ole32" name="ProgIDFromCLSID">
    <documentation>
      <desc>Retrieves the ProgID for a given CLSID</desc>
      <remarks>
	Every OLE object class listed in the Insert Object dialog box
	must have a programmatic identifier (ProgID), a string that
	uniquely identifies a given class, stored in the registry. In
	addition to determining the eligibility for the Insert Object
	dialog box, the ProgID can be used as an identifier in a macro
	programming language to identify a class. Finally, the ProgID
	is also the class name used for an object of an OLE class that
	is placed in an OLE 1 container.  ProgIDFromCLSID uses entries
	in the registry to do the conversion. OLE application authors
	are responsible for ensuring that the registry is configured
	correctly in the application's setup program.  The ProgID
	string must be different than the class name of any OLE 1
	application, including the OLE 1 version of the same
	application, if there is one. In addition, a ProgID string
	must not contain more than 39 characters, start with a digit,
	or, except for a single period, contain any punctuation
	(including underscores).  The ProgID must never be shown to
	the user in the user interface. If you need a short
	displayable string for an object, call
	IOleObject::GetUserType.  Call the CLSIDFromProgID function to
	find the CLSID associated with a given ProgID. Be sure to free
	the returned ProgID when you are finished with it by calling
	the CoTaskMemFree function.
      </remarks>
      <apidoc>
        <pt>
          <ll>HRESULT ProgIDFromCLSID(</ll>
          <ld>_In_  REFCLSID clsid</ld>
          <ld>_Out_ LPOLESTR *lplpszProgID</ld>
          <ll>)</ll>
        </pt>
        <par name="clsid">
	  The CLSID for which the ProgID is to be requested
	</par>
        <par name="lplpszProgID">
	  The address of a pointer variable that receives the ProgID
	  string. The string that represents clsid includes enclosing
	  braces.
	</par>
        <return>
          <rc cond="success">S_OK</rc>
          <rc cond="failure">error code</rc>
        </return>
      </apidoc>
    </documentation>
    <api adj="8" cc="stdcall" name="ProgIDFromCLSID">
      <par loc="stack" name="clsid" io="r" nr="1">
        <type>REFCLSID</type>
	<roles>
	  <role rt="ioc:com" rn="clsid"/>
	</roles>
      </par>
      <par loc="stack" name="lplpszProgID" io="w" nr="2" rep="hex">
        <type><ptr><ptr>OLESTR</ptr></ptr></type>
	<pre><deref-write/></pre>
	<sideeffects><block-write/></sideeffects>
	<roles>
	  <role rt="ioc:com" rn="infox:progid"/>
	</roles>
      </par>
      <returntype>HRESULT</returntype>
    </api>
    <semantics>
      <io-actions>
        <io-action cat="com" desc="retrieves the programmatic identifier of an OLE class"/>
      </io-actions>
      <preconditions/>
      <postconditions/>
      <sideeffects/>
    </semantics>
  </libfun>
  <copyright-notice>Copyright 2012-2016, Kestrel Technology LLC, Palo Alto, CA 94304</copyright-notice>
</codehawk-binary-analyzer>
