<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
 <codehawk-binary-analyzer>
  <reference href="http://msdn.microsoft.com/"/>
  <header date="03/26/2015 12:31:09"/>
  <symbolic-constants type="format_message_flags">
    <type>format_message_flags</type>
    <values>
      <symf name="FORMAT_MESSAGE_ALLOCATE_BUFFER" value="0x00000100">
	<desc>
	  The function allocates a buffer large enough to hold the formatted message,
	  and places a pointer to the allocated buffer at the address specified by 
	  lpBuffer. The lpBuffer parameter is a pointer to an LPTSTR; you must cast 
	  the pointer to an LPTSTR. The nSize parameter specifies the minimum number
	  of TCHARs to allocate for an output message buffer. The caller should use 
	  the LocalFree function to free the buffer when it is no longer needed.
	</desc>
      </symf>
      <symf name="FORMAT_MESSAGE_ARGUMENT_ARRAY" value="0x00002000">
	<desc>
	  The Arguments parameter is not a va_list structure, but is a pointer to an 
	  array of values that represent the arguments.
	</desc>
      </symf>
      <symf name="FORMAT_MESSAGE_FROM_HMODULE" value="0x00000800">
	<desc>
	  The lpSource parameter is a module handle containing the message-table 
	  resource(s) to search. If this lpSource handle is NULL, the current 
	  process's application image file will be searched. This flag cannot be 
	  used with FORMAT_MESSAGE_FROM_STRING.
	</desc>
      </symf>
      <symf name="FORMAT_MESSAGE_FROM_STRING" value="0x00000400">
	<desc>
	  The lpSource parameter is a pointer to a null-terminated string that 
	  contains a message definition. The message definition may contain insert
	  sequences, just as the message text in a message table resource may. This 
	  flag cannot be used with FORMAT_MESSAGE_FROM_HMODULE or 
	  FORMAT_MESSAGE_FROM_SYSTEM.
	</desc>
      </symf>
      <symf name="FORMAT_MESSAGE_FROM_SYSTEM" value="0x00001000">
	<desc>
	  The function should search the system message-table resource(s) for the 
	  requested message. If this flag is specified with FORMAT_MESSAGE_FROM_HMODULE, 
	  the function searches the system message table if the message is not found 
	  in the module specified by lpSource. This flag cannot be used with 
	  FORMAT_MESSAGE_FROM_STRING.
	</desc>
      </symf>
      <symf name="FORMAT_MESSAGE_IGNORE_INSERTS" value="0x00000200">
	<desc>
	  Insert sequences in the message definition are to be ignored and passed 
	  through to the output buffer unchanged. This flag is useful for fetching
	  a message for later formatting. If this flag is set, the Arguments
	  parameter is ignored.
	</desc>
      </symf>
    </values>
  </symbolic-constants>
  <copyright-notice>Copyright 2012-2015, Kestrel Technology LLC, Palo Alto, CA 94304</copyright-notice>
 </codehawk-binary-analyzer>
