<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
 <codehawk-binary-analyzer>
  <reference href="http://msdn.microsoft.com/"/>
  <header date="11/19/2015 23:15:35"/>
  <symbolic-constants type="internet_option_constants">
   <values>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_BYPASS_EDITED_ENTRY" value="64">
     <desc>
       Sets or retrieves the Boolean value that determines if the
       system should check the network for newer content and overwrite
       edited cache entries if a newer version is found. If set to
       True, the system checks the network for newer content and
       overwrites the edited cache entry with the newer version. The
       default is False, which indicates that the edited cache entry
       should be used without checking the network.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_CACHE_TIMESTAMPS" value="69">
     <desc>
       Retrieves an INTERNET_CACHE_TIMESTAMPS structure that contains
       the LastModified time and Expires time from the resource stored
       in the Internet cache. This value is used by
       InternetQueryOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_CALLBACK" value="1">
     <desc>
       Sets or retrieves the address of the callback function defined
       for this handle. This option can be used on all HINTERNET
       handles. Used by InternetQueryOption and InternetSetOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_CLIENT_CERT_CONTEXT" value="84">
     <desc>
       This flag is not supported by InternetQueryOption. The lpBuffer
       parameter must be a pointer to a CERT_CONTEXT structure and not
       a pointer to a CERT_CONTEXT pointer. If an application receives
       ERROR_INTERNET_CLIENT_AUTH_CERT_NEEDED, it must call
       InternetErrorDlg or use InternetSetOption to supply a
       certificate before retrying the
       request. CertDuplicateCertificateContext is then called so that
       the certificate context passed can be independently released by
       the application.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_CODEPAGE" value="68">
     <desc>
       By default, the host or authority portion of the Unicode URL is
       encoded according to the IDN specification. Setting this option
       on the request, or connection handle, when IDN is disabled,
       specifies a code page encoding scheme for the host portion of
       the URL. The lpBuffer parameter in the call to
       InternetSetOption contains the desired DBCS code page. If no
       code page is specified in lpBuffer, WinINet uses the default
       system code page (CP_ACP). Note: This option is ignored if IDN
       is not disabled. For more information about how to disable IDN,
       see the INTERNET_OPTION_IDN option.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_CODEPAGE_PATH" value="100">
     <desc>
       By default, the path portion of the URL is UTF8 encoded. The
       WinINet API performs escape character (%) encoding on the
       high-bit characters. Setting this option on the request, or
       connection handle, disables the UTF8 encoding and sets a
       specific code page. The lpBuffer parameter in the call to
       InternetSetOption contains the desired DBCS codepage for the
       path. If no code page is specified in lpBuffer, WinINet uses
       the default CP_UTF8.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_CODEPAGE_EXTRA" value="101">
     <desc>
       By default, the path portion of the URL is the default system
       code page (CP_ACP). The escape character (%) conversions are
       not performed on the extra portion. Setting this option on the
       request, or connection handle disables the CP_ACP encoding. The
       lpBuffer parameter in the call to InternetSetOption contains
       the desired DBCS codepage for the extra portion of the URL. If
       no code page is specified in lpBuffer, WinINet uses the default
       system code page (CP_ACP).
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_COMPRESSED_CONTENT_LENGTH" value="147">
     <desc>
       Retrieves an unsigned long integer value that contains the
       size, in bytes, of the compressed content length. This option
       can only be queried by InternetQueryOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_CONNECT_RETRIES" value="3">
     <desc>
       Sets or retrieves an unsigned long integer value that contains
       the number of times WinINet attempts to resolve and connect to
       a host. It only attempts once per IP address. For example, if
       you attempt to connect to a multihome host that has ten IP
       addresses and INTERNET_OPTION_CONNECT_RETRIES is set to seven,
       WinINet only attempts to resolve and connect to the first seven
       IP addresses. Conversely, given the same set of ten IP
       addresses, if INTERNET_OPTION_CONNECT_RETRIES is set to 20,
       WinINet attempts each of the ten only once. If a host has only
       one IP address and the first connection attempt fails, there
       are no further attempts. If a connection attempt still fails
       after the specified number of attempts, the request is
       canceled. The default value for INTERNET_OPTION_CONNECT_RETRIES
       is five attempts. This option can be used on any HINTERNET
       handle, including a NULL handle. It is used by
       InternetQueryOption and InternetSetOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_CONNECT_TIMEOUT" value="2">
     <desc>
       Sets or retrieves an unsigned long integer value that contains
       the time-out value, in milliseconds, to use for Internet
       connection requests. Setting this option to infinite
       (0xFFFFFFFF) will disable this timer.  If a connection request
       takes longer than this time-out value, the request is
       canceled. When attempting to connect to multiple IP addresses
       for a single host (a multihome host), the timeout limit is
       cumulative for all of the IP addresses. This option can be used
       on any HINTERNET handle, including a NULL handle. It is used by
       InternetQueryOption and InternetSetOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_CONNECTED_STATE" value="50">
     <desc>
       Sets or retrieves an unsigned long integer value that contains
       the connected state. This is used by InternetQueryOption and
       InternetSetOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_CONTEXT_VALUE" value="45">
     <desc>
       Sets or retrieves a DWORD_PTR that contains the address of the
       context value associated with this HINTERNET handle. This
       option can be used on any HINTERNET handle. This is used by
       InternetQueryOption and InternetSetOption. Previously, this set
       the context value to the address stored in the lpBuffer
       pointer. This has been corrected so that the value stored in
       the buffer is used and the INTERNET_OPTION_CONTEXT_VALUE flag
       is assigned a new value. The old value, 10, has been preserved
       so that applications written for the old behavior are still
       supported.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_CONTROL_RECEIVE_TIMEOUT" value="6">
     <desc>
       Identical to INTERNET_OPTION_RECEIVE_TIMEOUT. This is used by
       InternetQueryOption and InternetSetOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_CONTROL_SEND_TIMEOUT" value="5">
     <desc>
       Identical to INTERNET_OPTION_SEND_TIMEOUT. This is used by
       InternetQueryOption and InternetSetOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_DATA_RECEIVE_TIMEOUT" value="8">
     <desc>
       Sets or retrieves an unsigned long integer value that contains
       the time-out value, in milliseconds, to receive a response to a
       request for the data channel of an FTP transaction. If the
       response takes longer than this time-out value, the request is
       canceled. This option can be used on any HINTERNET handle,
       including a NULL handle. It is used by InternetQueryOption and
       InternetSetOption.  This flag has no impact on HTTP
       functionality.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_DATA_SEND_TIMEOUT" value="7">
     <desc>
       Sets or retrieves an unsigned long integer value, in
       milliseconds, that contains the time-out value to send a
       request for the data channel of an FTP transaction. If the send
       takes longer than this time-out value, the send is
       canceled. This option can be used on any HINTERNET handle,
       including a NULL handle. It is used by InternetQueryOption and
       InternetSetOption.  This flag has no impact on HTTP
       functionality.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_DATAFILE_NAME" value="33">
     <desc>
       Retrieves a string value that contains the name of the file
       backing a downloaded entity. This flag is valid after
       InternetOpenUrl, FtpOpenFile, GopherOpenFile, or
       HttpOpenRequest has completed. This option can only be queried
       by InternetQueryOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_DATAFILE_EXT" value="96">
     <desc>
       Sets a string value that contains the extension of the file
       backing a downloaded entity. This flag should be set before
       calling InternetOpenUrl, FtpOpenFile, GopherOpenFile, or
       HttpOpenRequest. This option can only be set by
       InternetSetOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_DIAGNOSTIC_SOCKET_INFO" value="67">
     <desc>
       Retrieves an INTERNET_DIAGNOSTIC_SOCKET_INFO structure that
       contains data about a specified HTTP Request. This flag is used
       by InternetQueryOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_DIGEST_AUTH_UNLOAD" value="76">
     <desc>
       Causes the system to log off the Digest authentication SSPI
       package, purging all of the credentials created for the
       process. No buffer is required for this option. It is used by
       InternetSetOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_END_BROWSER_SESSION" value="42">
     <desc>
       Flushes entries not in use from the password cache on the hard
       disk drive. Also resets the cache time used when the
       synchronization mode is once-per-session. No buffer is required
       for this option. This is used by InternetSetOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_ERROR_MASK" value="62">
     <desc>
       Sets an unsigned long integer value that contains the error
       masks that can be handled by the client application
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_EXTENDED_ERROR" value="24">
     <desc>
       Retrieves an unsigned long integer value that contains a
       Winsock error code mapped to the ERROR_INTERNET_ error messages
       last returned in this thread context. This option is used on a
       NULLHINTERNET handle by InternetQueryOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_FROM_CACHE_TIMEOUT" value="63">
     <desc>
       Sets or retrieves an unsigned long integer value that contains
       the amount of time the system should wait for a response to a
       network request before checking the cache for a copy of the
       resource. If a network request takes longer than the time
       specified and the requested resource is available in the cache,
       the resource is retrieved from the cache. This is used by
       InternetQueryOption and InternetSetOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_HANDLE_TYPE" value="9">
     <desc>
       Retrieves an unsigned long integer value that contains the type
       of the HINTERNET handles passed in. This is used by
       InternetQueryOption on any HINTERNET handle
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_HTTP_DECODING" value="65">
     <desc>
       Enables WinINet to perform decoding for the gzip and deflate
       encoding schemes. For more information, see Content Encoding.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_HTTP_VERSION" value="59">
     <desc>
       Sets or retrieves an HTTP_VERSION_INFO structure that contains
       the supported HTTP version. This must be used on a NULL
       handle. This is used by InternetQueryOption and
       InternetSetOption.  On Windows 7, Windows Server 2008 R2, and
       later, the value of the dwMinorVersion member in the
       HTTP_VERSION_INFO structure is overridden by Internet Explorer
       settings. EnableHttp1_1 is a registry value under
       HKLM\Software\Microsoft\InternetExplorer\AdvacnedOptions\HTTP\GENABLE
       controlled by Internet Options set in Internet Explorer for the
       system. The EnableHttp1_1 value defaults to 1. The
       HTTP_VERSION_INFO structure is ignored for any HTTP version
       less than 1.1 if EnableHttp1_1 is set to 1.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_IDN" value="102">
     <desc>
       By default, the host or authority portion of the URL is encoded
       according to the IDN specification for both direct and proxy
       connections. This option can be used on the request, or
       connection handle to enable or disable IDN. When IDN is
       disabled, WinINet uses the system codepage to encode the host
       or authority portion of the URL. To disable IDN host
       conversion, set the lpBuffer parameter in the call to
       InternetSetOption to zero. To enable IDN conversion on only the
       direct connection, specify INTERNET_FLAG_IDN_DIRECT in the
       lpBuffer parameter in the call to InternetSetOption. To enable
       IDN conversion on only the proxy connection, specify
       INTERNET_FLAG_IDN_PROXY in the lpBuffer parameter in the call
       to InternetSetOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_IGNORE_OFFLINE" value="77">
     <desc>
       Sets or retrieves whether the global offline flag should be
       ignored for the specified request handle. No buffer is required
       for this option. This is used by InternetQueryOption and
       InternetSetOption with a request handle. This option is only
       valid in Internet Explorer 5 and later.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_MAX_CONNS_PER_1_0_SERVER" value="74">
     <desc>
       Sets or retrieves an unsigned long integer value that contains
       the maximum number of connections allowed per HTTP/1.0
       server. This is used by InternetQueryOption and
       InternetSetOption. This option is only valid in Internet
       Explorer 5 and later.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_MAX_CONNS_PER_PROXY" value="103">
     <desc>
       Sets or retrieves an unsigned long integer value that contains
       the maximum number of connections allowed per CERN proxy. When
       this option is set or retrieved, the hInternet parameter must
       set to a null handle value. A null handle value indicates that
       the option should be set or queried for the current
       process. When calling InternetSetOption with this option, all
       existing proxy objects will receive the new value. This value
       is limited to a range of 2 to 128, inclusive.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_MAX_CONNS_PER_SERVER" value="73">
     <desc>
       Sets or retrieves an unsigned long integer value that contains
       the maximum number of connections allowed per server. This is
       used by InternetQueryOption and InternetSetOption. This option
       is only valid in Internet Explorer 5 and later.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_PARENT_HANDLE" value="21">
     <desc>
       Retrieves the parent handle to this handle. This option can be
       used on any HINTERNET handle by InternetQueryOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_PASSWORD" value="29">
     <desc>
       Sets or retrieves a string value that contains the password
       associated with a handle returned by InternetConnect. This is
       used by InternetQueryOption and InternetSetOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_PER_CONNECTION_OPTION" value="75">
     <desc>
       Sets or retrieves an INTERNET_PER_CONN_OPTION_LIST structure
       that specifies a list of options for a particular
       connection. This is used by InternetQueryOption and
       InternetSetOption. This option is only valid in Internet
       Explorer 5 and later.  Note
       INTERNET_OPTION_PER_CONNECTION_OPTION causes the settings to be
       changed on a system-wide basis when a NULL handle is used in
       the call to InternetSetOption. To refresh the global proxy
       settings, you must call InternetSetOption with the
       INTERNET_OPTION_REFRESH option flag.  Note To change proxy
       information for the entire process without affecting the global
       settings in Internet Explorer 5 and later, use this option on
       the handle that is returned from InternetOpen. The following
       code example changes the proxy for the whole process even
       though the HINTERNET handle is closed and is not used by any
       requests.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_PROXY" value="38">
     <desc>
       Sets or retrieves an INTERNET_PROXY_INFO structure that
       contains the proxy data for an existing InternetOpen handle
       when the HINTERNET handle is not NULL. If the HINTERNET handle
       is NULL, the function sets or queries the global proxy
       data. This option can be used on the handle returned by
       InternetOpen. It is used by InternetQueryOption and
       InternetSetOption.  Note It is recommended that
       INTERNET_OPTION_PER_CONNECTION_OPTION be used instead of
       INTERNET_OPTION_PROXY
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_PROXY_PASSWORD" value="44">
     <desc>
       Sets or retrieves a string value that contains the password
       used to access the proxy. This is used by InternetQueryOption
       and InternetSetOption. This option can be set on the handle
       returned by InternetConnect or HttpOpenRequest.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_PROXY_SETTINGS_CHANGED" value="95">
     <desc>
       Alerts the current WinInet instance that proxy settings have
       changed and that they must update with the new settings. To
       alert all available WinInet instances, set the Buffer parameter
       of InternetSetOption to NULL and BufferLength to 0 when passing
       this option. This option can be set on the handle returned by
       InternetConnect or HttpOpenRequest.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_PROXY_USERNAME" value="43">
     <desc>
       Sets or retrieves a string value that contains the user name
       used to access the proxy. This is used by InternetQueryOption
       and InternetSetOption. This option can be set on the handle
       returned by InternetConnect or HttpOpenRequest.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_READ_BUFFER_SIZE" value="12">
     <desc>
       Sets or retrieves an unsigned long integer value that contains
       the size of the read buffer. This option can be used on
       HINTERNET handles returned by FtpOpenFile, FtpFindFirstFile,
       and InternetConnect (FTP session only). This option is used by
       InternetQueryOption and InternetSetOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_RECEIVE_TIMEOUT" value="6">
     <desc>
       Sets or retrieves an unsigned long integer value that contains
       the time-out value, in milliseconds, to receive a response to a
       request. If the response takes longer than this time-out value,
       the request is canceled. This option can be used on any
       HINTERNET handle, including a NULL handle. It is used by
       InternetQueryOption and InternetSetOption.  When used in
       reference to an FTP transaction, this option refers to the
       control channel.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_REFRESH" value="37">
     <desc>
       Causes the proxy data to be reread from the registry for a
       handle. No buffer is required. This option can be used on the
       HINTERNET handle returned by InternetOpen. It is used by
       InternetSetOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_REQUEST_FLAGS" value="23">
     <desc>
       Retrieves an unsigned long integer value that contains the
       special status flags that indicate the status of the download
       in progress. This is used by InternetQueryOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_REQUEST_PRIORITY" value="58">
     <desc>
       Sets or retrieves an unsigned long integer value that contains
       the priority of requests that compete for a connection on an
       HTTP handle. This is used by InternetQueryOption and
       InternetSetOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_RESET_URLCACHE_SESSION" value="60">
     <desc>
       Starts a new cache session for the process. No buffer is
       required. This is used by InternetSetOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_SECONDARY_CACHE_KEY" value="53">
     <desc>
       Sets or retrieves a string value that contains the secondary
       cache key. This is used by InternetQueryOption and
       InternetSetOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_SECURITY_CERTIFICATE" value="35">
     <desc>
       Retrieves the certificate for an SSL/PCT (Secure Sockets
       Layer/Private Communications Technology) server into a
       formatted string. This is used by InternetQueryOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_SECURITY_CERTIFICATE_STRUCT" value="32">
     <desc>
       Retrieves the certificate for an SSL/PCT server into the
       INTERNET_CERTIFICATE_INFO structure. This is used by
       InternetQueryOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_SECURITY_FLAGS" value="31">
     <desc>
       Retrieves an unsigned long integer value that contains the
       security flags for a handle. This option is used by
       InternetQueryOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_SECURITY_KEY_BITNESS" value="36">
     <desc>
       Retrieves an unsigned long integer value that contains the bit
       size of the encryption key. The larger the number, the greater
       the encryption strength used. This is used by
       InternetQueryOption. Be aware that the data retrieved this way
       relates to a transaction that has already occurred, whose
       security level can no longer be changed.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_SEND_TIMEOUT" value="5">
     <desc>
       Sets or retrieves an unsigned long integer value, in
       milliseconds, that contains the time-out value to send a
       request. If the send takes longer than this time-out value, the
       send is canceled. This option can be used on any HINTERNET
       handle, including a NULL handle. It is used by
       InternetQueryOption and InternetSetOption.  When used in
       reference to an FTP transaction, this option refers to the
       control channel.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_SERVER_CERT_CHAIN_CONTEXT" value="105">
     <desc>
       Retrieves the server's certificate-chain context as a
       duplicated PCCERT_CHAIN_CONTEXT. You may pass this duplicated
       context to any Crypto API function which takes a
       PCCERT_CHAIN_CONTEXT. You must call CertFreeCertificateChain on
       the returned PCCERT_CHAIN_CONTEXT when you are done with the
       certificate-chain context.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_SETTINGS_CHANGED" value="39">
     <desc>
       Notifies the system that the registry settings have been
       changed so that it verifies the settings on the next call to
       InternetConnect. This is used by InternetSetOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_SUPPRESS_SERVER_AUTH" value="104">
     <desc>
       Sets an HTTP request object such that it will not logon to
       origin servers, but will perform automatic logon to HTTP proxy
       servers. This option differs from the Request flag
       INTERNET_FLAG_NO_AUTH, which prevents authentication to both
       proxy servers and origin servers.  Setting this mode will
       suppress the use of any credential material (either previously
       provided username/password or client SSL certificate) when
       communicating with an origin server. However, if the request
       must transit via an authenticating proxy, WinINet will still
       perform automatic authentication to the HTTP proxy per the
       Intranet Zone settings for the user. The default Intranet Zone
       setting is to permit automatic logon using the user's default
       credentials.  To ensure suppression of all identifying
       information, the caller should combine
       INTERNET_OPTION_SUPPRESS_SERVER_AUTH with the
       INTERNET_FLAG_NO_COOKIES request flag.  This option may only be
       set on request objects before they have been sent. Attempts to
       set this option after the request has been sent will return
       ERROR_INTERNET_INCORRECT_HANDLE_STATE.  No buffer is required
       for this option. This is used by InternetSetOption on handles
       returned by HttpOpenRequest only.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_SUPPRESS_BEHAVIOR" value="81">
     <desc>
       A general purpose option that is used to suppress behaviors on
       a process-wide basis. The lpBuffer parameter of the function
       must be a pointer to a DWORD containing the specific behavior
       to suppress. This option cannot be queried with
       InternetQueryOption. The permitted values are:
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_URL" value="34">
     <desc>
       Retrieves a string value that contains the full URL of a
       downloaded resource. If the original URL contained any extra
       data, such as search strings or anchors, or if the call was
       redirected, the URL returned differs from the original. This
       option is valid on HINTERNET handles returned by
       InternetOpenUrl, FtpOpenFile, GopherOpenFile, or
       HttpOpenRequest. It is used by InternetQueryOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_USER_AGENT" value="41">
     <desc>
       Sets or retrieves the user agent string on handles supplied by
       InternetOpen and used in subsequent HttpSendRequest functions,
       as long as it is not overridden by a header added by
       HttpAddRequestHeaders or HttpSendRequest. This is used by
       InternetQueryOption and InternetSetOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_USERNAME" value="28">
     <desc>
       Sets or retrieves a string that contains the user name
       associated with a handle returned by InternetConnect. This is
       used by InternetQueryOption and InternetSetOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_VERSION" value="40">
     <desc>
       Retrieves an INTERNET_VERSION_INFO structure that contains the
       version number of Wininet.dll. This option can be used on a
       NULLHINTERNET handle by InternetQueryOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="INTERNET_OPTION_WRITE_BUFFER_SIZE" value="13">
     <desc>
       Sets or retrieves an unsigned long integer value that contains
       the size, in bytes, of the write buffer. This option can be
       used on HINTERNET handles returned by FtpOpenFile and
       InternetConnect (FTP session only). It is used by
       InternetQueryOption and InternetSetOption.
     </desc>
    </symc>
   </values>
  </symbolic-constants>
  <copyright-notice>Copyright 2012-2020, Kestrel Technology LLC, Palo Alto, CA 94304</copyright-notice>
 </codehawk-binary-analyzer>
