<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
 <codehawk-binary-analyzer>
  <reference href="http://msdn.microsoft.com/"/>
  <header date="04/05/2015 15:07:42"/>
  <symbolic-constants type="logon_type">
    <type>logon_type</type>
    <values>
      <symc name="LOGON32_LOGON_INTERACTIVE" value="2">
	<desc>
	  intended for users who will be interactively using the computer, such 
	  as a user being logged on by a terminal server, remote shell, or similar 
	  process. This logon type has the additional expense of caching logon 
	  information for disconnected operations; therefore, it is inappropriate 
	  for some client/server applications, such as a mail server.
	</desc>
      </symc>
      <symc name="LOGON32_LOGON_NETWORK" value="3">
	<desc>
	  intended for high performance servers to authenticate plaintext passwords. 
	  The LogonUserExExW function does not cache credentials for this logon type.
	</desc>
      </symc>
      <symc name="LOGON32_LOGON_BATCH" value="4">
	<desc>
	  intended for batch servers, where processes may be executing on behalf of 
	  a user without their direct intervention. This type is also for higher 
	  performance servers that process many plaintext authentication attempts 
	  at a time, such as mail or web servers
	</desc>
      </symc>
      <symc name="LOGON32_LOGON_SERVICE" value="5">
	<desc>
	  Indicates a service-type logon. The account provided must have the service 
	  privilege enabled.
	</desc>
      </symc>
      <symc name="LOGON32_LOGON_UNLOCK" value="7">
	<desc>
	  for GINA DLLs that log on users who will be interactively using the computer. 
	  This logon type can generate a unique audit record that shows when the 
	  workstation was unlocked.
	</desc>
      </symc>
      <symc name="LOGON32_LOGON_NETWORK_CLEARTEXT" value="8">
	<desc>
	  preserves the name and password in the authentication package, which allows 
	  the server to make connections to other network servers while impersonating 
	  the client. A server can accept plaintext credentials from a client, call
	  LogonUserExExW, verify that the user can access the system across the 
	  network, and still communicate with other servers.
	</desc>
      </symc>
      <symc name="LOGON32_LOGON_NEW_CREDENTIALS" value="9">
	<desc>
	  allows the caller to clone its current token and specify new credentials 
	  for outbound connections. The new logon session has the same local 
	  identifier but uses different credentials for other network connections.
	  This logon type is supported only by the LOGON32_PROVIDER_WINNT50 logon 
	  provider.
	</desc>
      </symc>
    </values>
  </symbolic-constants>
  <copyright-notice>Copyright 2012-2015, Kestrel Technology LLC, Palo Alto, CA 94304</copyright-notice>
 </codehawk-binary-analyzer>
