<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
 <codehawk-binary-analyzer>
  <reference href="http://msdn.microsoft.com/"/>
  <header date="09/30/2015 11:53:22"/>
  <symbolic-constants type="predefined_registry_key_constants">
   <values>
    <symc name="HKEY_CLASSES_ROOT" value="0x80000000">
     <desc>
       Registry entries subordinate to this key define types (or classes) of 
       documents and the properties associated with those types. Shell and COM
       applications use the information stored under this key.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="HKEY_CURRENT_USER" value="0x80000001">
     <desc>
       Contains information about the current hardware profile of the local computer 
       system. The information under HKEY_CURRENT_CONFIG describes only the differences
       between the current hardware configuration and the standard configuration.
       Information about the standard hardware configuration is stored under the 
       Software and System keys of HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE" value="0x80000002">
     <desc>
       Registry entries subordinate to this key define the physical state of the
       computer, including data about the bus type, system memory, and installed 
       hardware and software. It contains subkeys that hold current configuration
       data, including Plug and Play information (the Enum branch, which includes 
       a complete list of all hardware that has ever been on the system), network
       logon preferences, network security information, software-related information 
       (such as server names and the location of the server), and other system 
       information.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="HKEY_USERS" value="0x80000003">
     <desc>
       Registry entries subordinate to this key define the default user configuration
       for new users on the local computer and the user configuration for the current 
       user.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="HKEY_PERFORMANCE_DATA" value="0x80000004">
     <desc>
       Registry entries subordinate to this key reference the text strings that
       describe counters in US English. These entries are not available to 
       Regedit.exe and Regedt32.exe.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="HKEY_CURRENT_CONFIG" value="0x80000005">
     <desc>
       Contains information about the current hardware profile of the local computer
       system. The information under HKEY_CURRENT_CONFIG describes only the differences 
       between the current hardware configuration and the standard configuration. 
       Information about the standard hardware configuration is stored under the 
       Software and System keys of HKEY_LOCAL_MACHINE.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="HKEY_DYN_DATA" value="0x80000006">
     <desc>
       ???Registry entries subordinate to this key define preferences of the current 
       user that are local to the machine. These entries are not included in the 
       per-user registry portion of a roaming user profile.???
     </desc>
    </symc>
   </values>
  </symbolic-constants>
  <copyright-notice>Copyright 2012-2016, Kestrel Technology LLC, Palo Alto, CA 94304</copyright-notice>
 </codehawk-binary-analyzer>
