<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
 <codehawk-binary-analyzer>
  <reference href="http://msdn.microsoft.com/"/>
  <header date="08/21/2015 21:57:22"/>
  <symbolic-flags type="service_access_rights_flags">
    <values>
      <symc name="SERVICE_ALL_ACCESS" value="0xF01FF">
	<desc>
	  Includes STANDARD_RIGHTS_REQUIRED in addition to all access rights in this table
	</desc>
      </symc>
      <symf name="SERVICE_CHANGE_CONFIG" value="0x0002">
	<desc>
	  Required to call the ChangeServiceConfig or ChangeServiceConfig2 function to
	  change the service configuration. Because this grants the caller the right 
	  to change the executable file that the system runs, it should be granted
	  only to administrators
	</desc>
      </symf>
      <symf name="SERVICE_ENUMERATE_DEPENDENTS" value="0x0008">
	<desc>
	  Required to call the EnumDependentServices function to enumerate all the 
	  services dependent on the service.
	</desc>
      </symf>
      <symf name="SERVICE_INTERROGATE" value="0x0080">
	<desc>
	  Required to call the ControlService function to ask the service to report
	  its status immediately
	</desc>
      </symf>
      <symf name="SERVICE_PAUSE_CONTINUE" value="0x0040">
	<desc>
	  Required to call the ControlService function to pause or continue the service
	</desc>
      </symf>
      <symf name="SERVICE_QUERY_CONFIG" value="0x0001">
	<desc>
	  Required to call the QueryServiceConfig and QueryServiceConfig2 functions to 
	  query the service configuration
	</desc>
      </symf>
      <symf name="SERVICE_QUERY_STATUS" value="0x0004">
	<desc>
	  Required to call the QueryServiceStatus or QueryServiceStatusEx function to 
	  ask the service control manager about the status of the service.
	  Required to call the NotifyServiceStatusChange function to receive notification 
	  when a service changes status.
	</desc>
      </symf>
      <symf name="SERVICE_START" value="0x0010">
	<desc>
	  Required to call the StartService function to start the service
	</desc>
      </symf>
      <symf name="SERVICE_STOP" value="0x0020">
	<desc>
	  Required to call the ControlService function to stop the service
	</desc>
      </symf>
      <symf name="SERVICE_USER_DEFINED_CONTROL" value="0x0100">
	<desc>
	  Required to call the ControlService function to specify a user-defined control code
	</desc>
      </symf>
    </values>
  </symbolic-flags>
  <copyright-notice>Copyright 2012-2015, Kestrel Technology LLC, Palo Alto, CA 94304</copyright-notice>
 </codehawk-binary-analyzer>
