<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
 <codehawk-binary-analyzer>
  <reference href="http://msdn.microsoft.com/"/>
  <header date="08/31/2015 17:52:25"/>
  <symbolic-constants type="show_command_constants">
   <values>
    <symc name="SW_HIDE" value="0x0">
     <desc>Hides the window and activates another window.</desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="SW_MAXIMIZE" value="0x3">
     <desc>Maximizes the specified window.</desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="SW_MINIMIZE" value="0x6">
     <desc>
       Minimizes the specified window and activates the next top-level window in the z-order.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="SW_RESTORE" value="0x9">
     <desc>
       Activates and displays the window. If the window is minimized or maximized, 
       Windows restores it to its original size and position. An application should 
       specify this flag when restoring a minimized window.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="SW_SHOW" value="0x5">
     <desc>Activates the window and displays it in its current size and position.</desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="SW_SHOWDEFAULT" value="0xa">
     <desc>
       Sets the show state based on the SW_ flag specified in the STARTUPINFO structure 
       passed to the CreateProcess function by the program that started the application. 
       An application should call ShowWindow with this flag to set the initial show state 
       of its main window.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="SW_SHOWMINIMIZED" value="0x2">
     <desc>Activates the window and displays it as a minimized window</desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="SW_SHOWMINNOACTIVE" value="0x7">
     <desc>
       Displays the window as a minimized window. The active window remains active
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="SW_SHOWNA" value="0x8">
     <desc>
       Displays the window in its current state. The active window remains active
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="SW_SHOWNOACTIVATE" value="0x4">
     <desc>
       Displays a window in its most recent size and position. The active window remains active.
     </desc>
    </symc>
    <symc name="SW_SHOWNORMAL" value="0x1">
     <desc>
       Activates and displays a window. If the window is minimized or maximized, Windows 
       restores it to its original size and position. An application should specify this 
       flag when displaying the window for the first time.
     </desc>
    </symc>
   </values>
  </symbolic-constants>
  <copyright-notice>Copyright 2012-2015, Kestrel Technology LLC, Palo Alto, CA 94304</copyright-notice>
 </codehawk-binary-analyzer>
