<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
 <codehawk-binary-analyzer>
  <reference href="http://msdn.microsoft.com/"/>
  <header date="11/05/2015 12:02:57"/>
  <symbolic-constants type="window_positioning_flags">
   <values>
    <symf name="SWP_ASYNCWINDOWPOS" value="0x4000">
     <desc>
       If the calling thread and the thread that owns the window are attached to
       different input queues, the system posts the request to the thread that
       owns the window. This prevents the calling thread from blocking its 
       execution while other threads process the request.
     </desc>
    </symf>
    <symf name="SWP_DEFERERASE" value="0x2000">
     <desc>Prevents generation of the WM_SYNCPAINT message</desc>
    </symf>
    <symf name="SWP_DRAWFRAME" value="0x0020">
     <desc>
       Draws a frame (defined in the window's class description) around the window
     </desc>
    </symf>
    <symf name="SWP_FRAMECHANGED" value="0x0020">
     <desc>
       Applies new frame styles set using the SetWindowLong function. Sends a
       WM_NCCALCSIZE message to the window, even if the window's size is not 
       being changed. If this flag is not specified, WM_NCCALCSIZE is sent 
       only when the window's size is being changed.
     </desc>
    </symf>
    <symf name="SWP_HIDEWINDOW" value="0x0080">
     <desc>Hides the window</desc>
    </symf>
    <symf name="SWP_NOACTIVATE" value="0x0010">
     <desc>
       Does not activate the window. If this flag is not set, the window is 
       activated and moved to the top of either the topmost or non-topmost
       group (depending on the setting of the hWndInsertAfter parameter).
     </desc>
    </symf>
    <symf name="SWP_NOCOPYBITS" value="0x0100">
     <desc>
       Discards the entire contents of the client area. If this flag is not 
       specified, the valid contents of the client area are saved and copied
       back into the client area after the window is sized or repositioned.
     </desc>
    </symf>
    <symf name="SWP_NOMOVE" value="0x0002">
     <desc>Retains the current position (ignores X and Y parameters)</desc>
    </symf>
    <symf name="SWP_NOREPOSITION" value="0x0200">
     <desc>Does not change the owner window's position in the Z order</desc>
    </symf>
    <symf name="SWP_NOREDRAW" value="0x0008">
     <desc>
       Does not redraw changes. If this flag is set, no repainting of any 
       kind occurs. This applies to the client area, the nonclient area 
       (including the title bar and scroll bars), and any part of the 
       parent window uncovered as a result of the window being moved. 
       When this flag is set, the application must explicitly invalidate 
       or redraw any parts of the window and parent window that need redrawing.
     </desc>
    </symf>
    <symf name="SWP_NOSENDCHANGING" value="0x0400">
     <desc>
       Prevents the window from receiving the WM_WINDOWPOSCHANGING message
     </desc>
    </symf>
    <symf name="SWP_NOSIZE" value="0x0001">
     <desc>Retains the current size (ignores the cx and cy parameters)</desc>
    </symf>
    <symf name="SWP_NOZORDER" value="0x0004">
     <desc>
       Retains the current Z order (ignores the hWndInsertAfter parameter)
     </desc>
    </symf>
    <symf name="SWP_SHOWWINDOW" value="0x0040">
     <desc>Displays the window</desc>
    </symf>
   </values>
  </symbolic-constants>
  <copyright-notice>Copyright 2012-2015, Kestrel Technology LLC, Palo Alto, CA 94304</copyright-notice>
 </codehawk-binary-analyzer>
